Erol BicerNuclear Engineer



- +82-10-7497-0705
- ✓ erolbicer@live.com
- South Korea
- 1989 September 29
- www.erolbicer.com
- in LinkedIn
- R^G ResearchGate

LANGUAGES	
English • Turkish	• Korean
SYSTEM CODES	
RELAP5	
SNAP	
GOTHIC	
MARS-KS	
SPACE	
CAP	
CFD CODES	
OpenFOAM	
CUPID	

MISCELLANEOUS

PROGRAMMING CODES

DOS/UNIX
CATIA
Origin
ParaView

Mathcad
Git/GitHub
MS Office

MATLAB

FORTRAN

HTML/CSS

C++

PROFILE

Throughout my academic and professional career, I have focused on nuclear safety analyses at the plant, system, and component levels utilizing system safety analysis and computational fluid dynamics codes. I have experience with various baseload nuclear power plant technologies as well as small, and micro modular reactors.

EDUCATION

Nuclear Engineering, Ph.D., Seoul National University

2017 − present | Seoul, South Korea

Nuclear Power Plant Engineering, M.Sc., KINGS ☑ 2014 – 2016 | Ulsan, South Korea

Nuclear Energy Engineering, B.Sc., Hacettepe University

2008 − 2013 | Ankara, Turkey

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

FNC Technology Co., Ltd. \Box

Associate Manager 2016 – present | Suwon, South Korea

Assistant Manager

2016 - 2019 | Suwon, South Korea

Bil-Plas Industry and Trade Co., Ltd., R&D Engineer ☑ 2013 – 2014 | Ankara, Turkey

CERTIFICATES

Modelling and Computation of Multiphase Flows

Swiss Federal Institute of Technology (ETH)

International Marketing, Business Knowledge and IntelligenceAnkara Chamber of Commerce (ATO)

AWARDS

International Atomic Energy Agency Fellowship, IAEA

Full Academic Scholarship, KINGS

MAIN PROJECTS

[SMR] Small and Micro Modular Reactors Technology Analyses

[PCCS] Conceptual Design and Development of Passive Containment Cooling System for APR1400

[SMART] System-Integrated Modular Advanced Reactor Passive Containment Cooling System

[PGSFR] Prototype Gen-IV Sodium-Cooled Fast Reactor Condition Analysis Project

[PAFS] Passive Auxiliary Feedwater System Development

[ATLAS] Determination of ATLAS Heat Loss and Improvement of MARS Model

[EUR] APR1000 PAFS Standard Design Development and EUR Certification Support

More information can be found here **2**

PERSONAL VENTURES

Nuclear Industry Association of Turkey, Board of Directors ☑

Turkish Chamber of Commerce in Korea, Co-Founder ☑

Liviboard, Co-Founder ☑

Hacettepe Rugby Club, Founder ☑